Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Der Morgen Uniform Title: Morgen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 563 Engraver: Friedrich Kratzschmer, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614037; 64662 (Box 53, Folder 642)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Der Morgen Uniform Title: Morgen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 553 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612437; 64661 (Box 58, Folder 715)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Feramors. Balletmusik und Hochzeitszug Uniform Title: Feramors. Balletmusik und Hochzeitszug Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 1287 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612437; 64660 (Box 58, Folder 711)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Kamennoi-Ostrow. Album of 24 Portraits. No. 22 Uniform Title: Kamennoi-Ostrow, op. 10, no. 22 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 2984, undated; 31142040612890; 64659 (Box 104, Folder 1420)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Kamenoi Ostrow (Cloister Scene) Uniform Title: Kamenoi Ostrow; arr. Publisher information: New York: Ross Jungnickel Plate Number: 6-47, undated; 31142040612437; 64658 (Box 58, Folder 718)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Lichtertanz der Braute von Kaschmir Uniform Title: Feramors. Balletmusik und Hochzeitszug Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff Plate Number: 1200 1202, undated; 31142040612890; 64657 (Box 104, Folder 1412)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Liebesfeier Uniform Title: Liebesfeier Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina (Gustav Lewy, Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: G. L. 172 Engraver: Mever., undated; 31142040613310; 64656 (Box 165, Folder 2796)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Melancolie Uniform Title: Six Morceaux pour le piano. No. 1: Melancolie Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 203 204, undated; 31142040612890; 64655 (Box 104, Folder 1411)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Melodie en Fa Uniform Title: Melodie en Fa; arr. Publisher information: Paris (France): J. Hamelle Plate Number: 3494. H., undated; 31142040612437; 64654 (Box 58, Folder 714)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Melody in F Uniform Title: Melody in F Publisher information: New York: Armstrong Music Publishing Company (Teller, Sons and Dorner, New York [printer]), undated; 31142040612874; 64653 (Box 102, Folder 1337)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Molto Lento. Spharenmusik. Aus dem Quartett Op. 17. No. 2 Uniform Title: Quartets, strings, op. 17, no. 2, C minor. Molto lento Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: K.M.591., undated; 31142040612841; 64652 (Box 99, Folder 1258)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Molto Lento. Spharenmusik. Aus dem Quartett Op. 17. No. 2 Uniform Title: Quartets, strings, op. 17, no. 2, C minor. Molto lento Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.1276., undated; 31142040612841; 64651 (Box 99, Folder 1257)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Moses. Act III Uniform Title: Moses. Act III Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2043 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613310; 64650 (Box 165, Folder 2816)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Moses. Geistliche Oper in acht Bildern. Act III Uniform Title: Moses. Act III Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2045 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612767; 64649 (Box 91, Folder 1129)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Moses. Geistliche Oper in acht Bildern. Act IV Uniform Title: Moses. Act IV Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2050 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612767; 64648 (Box 91, Folder 1130)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Moses. Geistliche Oper in acht Bildern. Acts III, IV Uniform Title: Moses. Acts III, IV Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholff Senff (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2042 (Act III) 2047 (Act IV) Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612767; 64647 (Box 91, Folder 1131)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Pecheur napolitain et Napolitaine Uniform Title: Pecheur napolitain et Napolitaine; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1703-52, undated; 31142040612437; 64646 (Box 58, Folder 716)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Romance Uniform Title: Romance in E-flat, op. 44, no. 1 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 2170, undated; 31142040612841; 64645 (Box 99, Folder 1259)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Seraphic Song Uniform Title: Reve angelique; arr. Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 75850-23 + 2, undated; 31142040613252; 64644 (Box 171, Folder 3073)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: The Asra Uniform Title: Asra; arr. Publisher information: New York: The John Church Company Plate Number: 17161-3, undated; 31142040613476; 64643 (Box 149, Folder 2141)
  - Composer: Rubinstein, Anton Title: Toreadore et Andalouse Uniform Title: Toreadore et Andalouse; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1703-52, undated; 31142040612437; 64642 (Box 58, Folder 717)
  - Composer: Ruf, Adolf L. Title: Die Auswanderer Uniform Title: Auswanderer; arr. Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): E. Tiersch, undated; 31142040613468; 64641 (Box 150, Folder 2176)
  - Composer: Russian folk song Title: Einsames Gloeckchen Uniform Title: Einsames Gloeckchen, undated; 31142040613427; 64640 (Box 154, Folder 2391)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor, arr. Title: When Love is Kind Uniform Title: When Love is Kind Publisher information: New York: The John Church Company Plate Number: 18101-5, undated; 31142040613237; 64639 (Box 173, Folder 3164)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Auf Wiederseh'n Uniform Title: Auf Wiederseh'n Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 23278-7, undated; 31142040613476; 64638 (Box 149, Folder 2135)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Liebe Uniform Title: Liebe Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G.H.2728., undated; 31142040613328; 64637 (Box 164, Folder 2766)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Nachtgesang, op. 41 Uniform Title: Nachtgesang, op. 41, undated; 31142040612759; 64636 (Box 90, Folder 1126)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Nachtgesang Uniform Title: Nachtgesang, undated; 31142040613286; 64635 (Box 168, Folder 2912)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Schlummerliedchen Uniform Title: Schlummerliedchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 2731. Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613245; 64634 (Box 172, Folder 3093)
  - Composer: Saar, Louis Victor Title: Wechselgesang Uniform Title: Wechselgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2493, undated; 31142040613435; 64633 (Box 153, Folder 2338)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Danse Bacchanale from Samson and Delilah Uniform Title: Samson et Dalila. Bacchanale; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 19217-73, undated; 31142040612478; 64632 (Box 62, Folder 791)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Danse Macabre. Poeme Symphonique Uniform Title: Danse macabre (Symphonic poem) Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils (Delanchy et Cie. [printer]) Plate Number: D. and F. 2140, undated; 31142040612486; 64631 (Box 63, Folder 798)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Danse Macabre. Poeme Symphonique Uniform Title: Danse macabre (Symphonic poem) Publisher information: Paris (France): Durand, Schoenewek and Cie. (Delanchy [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie.2148, undated; 31142040612486; 64630 (Box 63, Folder 799)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Danse Macabre Uniform Title: Danse macabre (Symphonic poem); arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10252-59, undated; 31142040612486; 64629 (Box 63, Folder 801)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Danse Macabre Uniform Title: Danse macabre (Symphonic poem); arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10252-83, undated; 31142040612486; 64628 (Box 63, Folder 800)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Henry VIII. Ballet-Divertissement Uniform Title: Henry VIII. Ballet-Divertissement Publisher information: Paris (France): Durand, Schoenewerk and Cie. Plate Number: D.S. and Cie. 3151, undated; 31142040612478; 64627 (Box 62, Folder 796)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Horace Uniform Title: Horace, undated; 31142040612478; 64626 (Box 62, Folder 797)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Le Rouet d'Omphale Uniform Title: Rouet d'Omphale; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11751-71, undated; 31142040612486; 64625 (Box 63, Folder 804)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Marche Heroique Uniform Title: Marche Heroique Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22619-81, undated; 31142040612478; 64624 (Box 62, Folder 795)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Marche Heroique Uniform Title: Marche Heroique Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils (Delanchy, Dupre and Cie. [printer]) Plate Number: D. and F. 7454, undated; 31142040612478; 64623 (Box 62, Folder 794)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Marche Heroique Uniform Title: Marche Heroique Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand et Fils (Delanchy, Dupre and Cie. [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie. 1630, undated; 31142040612478; 64622 (Box 62, Folder 792)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Marche Heroique Uniform Title: Marche Heroique Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand et Fils (Delanchy, Dupre and Cie. [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie. 1691, undated; 31142040612478; 64621 (Box 62, Folder 793)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Samson et Dalila. Bacchanale Uniform Title: Samson et Dalila. Bacchanale Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils (Delanchy and Cie [printer]) Plate Number: D. S. et Cie. 2388, undated; 31142040612478; 64620 (Box 62, Folder 790)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Samson et Dalila. Bacchanale Uniform Title: Samson et Dalila. Bacchanale Publisher information: Paris (France): A. Durand and Fils (Delanchy and Cie [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie 2389b, undated; 31142040612478; 64619 (Box 62, Folder 789)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Samson et Delila. Danse des Pretresses de Dagon Uniform Title: Samson et Delila. Danse des Pretresses de Dagon Publisher information: Paris (France): Durand, Schoenewerk et Cie./A Durand and Fils (Delanchy [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. et Cie. 2390, undated; 31142040612486; 64618 (Box 63, Folder 803)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Samson et Delila. Danse des Pretresses de Dagon Uniform Title: Samson et Delila. Danse des Pretresses de Dagon Publisher information: Paris (France): Durand, Schoenewerk et Cie. Plate Number: D.S. et Cie. 2598.bis Engraver: L. Parent, undated; 31142040612486; 64617 (Box 63, Folder 802)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Spring Chorus Uniform Title: Samson et Delilah. Spring Chorus Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 10196, undated; 31142040613500; 64616 (Box 146, Folder 2061)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: The Swan Uniform Title: Carnaval des animaux. arr. Cygne Publisher information: New York: Century Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 2140-2, undated; 31142040613518; 64615 (Box 145, Folder 2034)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: The Swan Uniform Title: Carnaval des animaux. Cygne; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10899-14, undated; 31142040612486; 64614 (Box 63, Folder 805)
  - Composer: Saint-Saens, Camille Title: Une Nuit a Lisbonne Uniform Title: Nuit a Lisbonne Publisher information: Paris (France): Durand, Schoenewerk and Cie. (Delanchy [printer]) Plate Number: D.S. and Cie. 2864, undated; 31142040612486; 64613 (Box 63, Folder 806)
  - Composer: Samans, Carl, arr. Title: Die Auserwahlte Uniform Title: Auserwahlte; arr. Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt and Belder Plate Number: L. and B. 984, undated; 31142040613427; 64612 (Box 154, Folder 2393)
  - Composer: Sanford, Harold, arr. Title: Victor Herbert Favorites Uniform Title: Victor Herbert Favorites Publisher information: New York: M. Witmark and Sons Plate Number: 23645-104, undated; 31142040614292; 64611 (Box 27, Folder 315)
  - Composer: Saupe, Christian Gottlob Title: Spinnlied Uniform Title: Spinnlied Publisher information: Dresden (Germany): Theobald Dietrich (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 167 Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613252; 64610 (Box 171, Folder 3056)
  - Composer: Schaedel, B. Title: Wallisischer Schiffergesang Uniform Title: Wallisischer Schiffergesang Plate Number: 102, undated; 31142040613096; 64609 (Box 124, Folder 1807)
  - Composer: Schaffer, A. Title: Die Post im Walde Uniform Title: Post im Walde; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2507-35, undated; 31142040612965; 64608 (Box 111, Folder 1591)
  - Composer: Schaffer, H. Title: Das eig'ne Herz Uniform Title: Eig'ne Herz, undated; 31142040613229; 64607 (Box 174, Folder 3229)
  - Composer: Schaffer, H. Title: Durch den Wald Uniform Title: Durch den Wald Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Eduard Annecke Plate Number: 911, undated; 31142040613443; 64606 (Box 152, Folder 2254)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Mataswintha Uniform Title: Mataswintha. Selection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 20263, undated, undated; 31142040612866; 64605 (Box 101, Folder 1318)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Mataswintha Uniform Title: Mataswintha. Selection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.507., undated; 31142040613302; 64604 (Box 166, Folder 2849)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Polish National Dance Uniform Title: Polnische Tanze, op. 3; arr Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1593-28, undated; 31142040612486; 64603 (Box 63, Folder 807)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Polnischer Nationaltanz, op. 3, no. 1 Uniform Title: Polnische Tanze, op. 3; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.654., undated; 31142040612486; 64602 (Box 63, Folder 808)
  - Composer: Schiebold, Carl Title: Madel, schenk' ein! Uniform Title: Madel, schenk' ein! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg Plate Number: E. E. 4371, undated; 31142040613294; 64601 (Box 167, Folder 2875)
  - Composer: Schild, F. Title: The Band's Coming. March Uniform Title: D'Band Kommt Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1755-18, undated; 31142040613088; 64600 (Box 123, Folder 1777)
  - Composer: Schiller, Carl Title: O traume nur! Uniform Title: O traume nur! Publisher information: Coburg (Germany): C. Schiller (Engelmann and Muhlberg, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C. S. 2 Engraver: Engelmann and Muhlberg, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613286; 64599 (Box 168, Folder 2904)
  - Composer: Schjelderup, Gerhard, arr. Title: Sonntag auf der Alm Uniform Title: Pa Solen jeg ser Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14735 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613245; 64598 (Box 172, Folder 3096)
  - Composer: Schlesinger, L. Title: Un Modele Uniform Title: Modele Plate Number: L. S. 4., undated; 31142040612486; 64597 (Box 63, Folder 810)
  - Composer: Schlesinger, Sebastian B. Title: Auf Wiederseh'n! Uniform Title: Auf Wiederseh'n!, undated; 31142040613096; 64596 (Box 124, Folder 1790)
  - Composer: Schmelz, R. Title: Wilkommen zu Heinrich Zollner Uniform Title: Wilkommen zu Heinrich Zollner, undated; 31142040612965; 64595 (Box 111, Folder 1590)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Fruhlingsglaube Uniform Title: Fruhlingsglaube Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Schlesinger Buch- and Musikhandlung Plate Number: S. 8258, undated; 31142040613385; 64594 (Box 158, Folder 2524)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Traumerei Uniform Title: Traumerei Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 433 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612817; 64593 (Box 96, Folder 1195)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Traumerei Uniform Title: Traumerei Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 384 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612817; 64592 (Box 96, Folder 1196)
  - Composer: Schmid, Fr. J., arr. Title: Zweiundvierzig Soloquartette fur Mannerstimmen Uniform Title: Zweiundvierzig Soloquartette fur Mannerstimmen Publisher information: Freising (Germany): Franz Paul Datterer Plate Number: 2, undated; 31142040613229; 64591 (Box 174, Folder 3227)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22243-3, undated; 31142040613344; 64590 (Box 162, Folder 2690)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth and Co. Plate Number: E. S. and Co. 3103, undated; 31142040613344; 64589 (Box 162, Folder 2689)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 15987, undated; 31142040613344; 64588 (Box 162, Folder 2691)
  - Composer: Schmidt, Gustav Title: Carmosenella Uniform Title: Carmosenella Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2677. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613344; 64587 (Box 162, Folder 2694)
  - Composer: Schmidt, Gustave Title: Alibi. Komische Operette Uniform Title: Alibi Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): Hugo Pohle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: H. P. 523 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612643; 64586 (Box 79, Folder 1021)
  - Composer: Schmitt, Jacques Title: Quatre Etudes de Concert. No. 4. Etude de Chant Uniform Title: Quatre Etudes de Concert, op. 330, no. 4. Etude de Chant Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth and Co. (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 1223 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612841; 64585 (Box 99, Folder 1272)
  - Composer: Schmoll, A. Title: Cymbals and Castanets. Caprice Espagnol Uniform Title: Cymbals and Castanets. Caprice Espagnol Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 11914, undated; 31142040612874; 64584 (Box 102, Folder 1327)
  - Composer: Schmolzer, Jakob Eduard Title: Die Waldfee Uniform Title: Waldfee Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5769, undated; 31142040613237; 64583 (Box 173, Folder 3173)
  - Composer: Schneider, H. J. Title: Bienenhaus Marsch Uniform Title: Bienenhaus Publisher information: Prague (Czech Republic): Joh. Hoffmann Plate Number: 4419, undated; 31142040612957; 64582 (Box 110, Folder 1580)
  - Composer: Schneider, H. J. Title: The Bee Hive Uniform Title: Bienenhaus; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5066-17, undated; 31142040612957; 64581 (Box 110, Folder 1581)
  - Composer: Scholz, Bernhard Title: Das Siegesfest Uniform Title: Siegesfest Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 23782., undated; 31142040612833; 64580 (Box 98, Folder 1232)
  - Composer: Scholz, Bernhard Title: Standchen an eine Verlassene Uniform Title: Standchen an eine Verlassene Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): Julius Hainauer (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: J. 2593 H. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612858; 64579 (Box 100, Folder 1303)
  - Composer: Schonberger, John, Richard Coburn and Vincent Rose Title: Whispering Uniform Title: Whispering Publisher information: New York: Miller Music Corporation Plate Number: 491-2, undated; 31142040613518; 64578 (Box 145, Folder 2030)
  - Composer: Schrammel, Johann Title: Wien bleibt Wien! Uniform Title: Wien bleibt Wien! Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. 27235., undated; 31142040613070; 64577 (Box 122, Folder 1761)
  - Composer: Schrammel, Johann Title: Wien bleibt Wien Uniform Title: Wien bleibt Wien Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2519-5, undated; 31142040612882; 64576 (Box 103, Folder 1375)
  - Composer: Schrattenholz, Leo Title: Meine Gottin Uniform Title: Meine Gottin Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 11165, undated; 31142040613104; 64575 (Box 125, Folder 1810)
  - Composer: Schreck, Gust. E. Title: Lauf der Welt Uniform Title: Lauf der Welt Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6236-3, undated; 31142040613310; 64574 (Box 165, Folder 2801)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Abendfrieden Uniform Title: Abendfrieden; arr., undated; 31142040613237; 64573 (Box 173, Folder 3160)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Alphonso and Estrella. Overture Uniform Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 7407-49, undated; 31142040612502; 64572 (Box 65, Folder 845)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture Uniform Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. 45017, undated; 31142040612502; 64571 (Box 65, Folder 843)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Am Meer Uniform Title: Am Meer; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2507-35, undated; 31142040612965; 64570 (Box 111, Folder 1593)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ave Maria Uniform Title: Ave Maria; arr. Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 19623, undated; 31142040614029; 64569 (Box 54, Folder 651)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Der Lindenbaum Uniform Title: Lindenbaum, undated; 31142040613211; 64568 (Box 175, Folder 3253)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Der Lindenbaum Uniform Title: Lindenbaum Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): [illegible], undated; 31142040613237; 64567 (Box 173, Folder 3193)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth and Co. (F. W. Garbrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4936 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated; 31142040614029; 64566 (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth and Co. (F. W. Garbrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4976 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated; 31142040614029; 64565 (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth and Co. (F. W. Grabrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4935 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated; 31142040614029; 64564 (Box 54, Folder 652)